{
  "heading": "Identifying Proper and Improper Fraction.",
  "topics": [
    {
      "heading": "Identifying Proper and Improper Fraction.",
      "questions": [
        {
            "questionNo": 1,
            "question": "Max stumbled upon an ancient tablet inscribed with 7 5/10. What does this mixed fraction simplify to as an improper fraction?",
            "options": [
                "73/10",
                "74/10",
                "75/10",
                "76/10"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 2,
            "question": "At the end of their journey, Timmy, Jenny, and Max found a hidden scroll. Which fraction on the scroll was an improper fraction?",
            "options": [
                "990/999",
                "985/1000",
                "998/999",
                "1009/991"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 3,
            "question": "Timmy encountered a problem in Fraction Forest where he needed to convert 75/30​ to a mixed fraction. What is the correct answer for Timmy?",
            "options": [
                "2 10/30",
                "2 15/30",
                "2 20/30",
                "2 25/30"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 4,
            "question": "Jenny saw a butterfly with fractions on its wings. Which fraction on the butterfly's wings was an improper fraction?",
            "options": [
                "230/250",
                "310/300",
                "780/784",
                "410/450"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 5,
            "question": "Timmy, Jenny, and Max, while exploring Fraction Forest, found stones with carvings 541/530, 358/464, and 555/565 respectively. Identify the improper fraction.",
            "options": [
                "541/530",
                "358/464",
                "555/565",
                "None of the above"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 6,
            "question": "Timmy uncovered a hidden scroll with 20 7/9​. What is the improper fraction equivalent of this mixed fraction?",
            "options": [
                "186/9",
                "187/9",
                "188/9",
                "185/9"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 7,
            "question": "Timmy and Jenny combined their findings and encountered 5 9/5 engraved on a tree. What is this mixed fraction when converted to an improper fraction?",
            "options": [
                "33/5",
                "34/5",
                "35/5",
                "36/5"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 8,
            "question": "During their journey, Timmy found a flower with fractions on its petals. Which petal had an improper fraction?",
            "options": [
                "120/130",
                "100/120",
                "160/150",
                "130/140"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 9,
            "question": "Max collected some berries, each labeled with a fraction. Which berry had an improper fraction?",
            "options": [
                "113/110",
                "303/310",
                "450/457",
                "602/620"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 10,
            "question": "Jenny discovered a magical scroll with the fraction 3 3/11​. What is the improper fraction equivalent of this mixed fraction?",
            "options": [
                "34/11​",
                "35/11",
                "36/11",
                "37/11"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 11,
            "question": "Jenny found another relic showing 10 7/6. What is the improper fraction representation of this mixed fraction?",
            "options": [
                "67/6",
                "68/6",
                "66/6​",
                "65/6"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 12,
            "question": "Max stumbled upon a rock with a fraction etched into it. If the fraction was improper, what fraction did Max see?",
            "options": [
                "105/210",
                "130/260",
                "150/300",
                "180/90"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 13,
            "question": "Max was exploring the depths of Fraction Forest and came across 93/15​. What is 93/15 in mixed fraction form?",
            "options": [
                "6 1/15",
                "6 2/15",
                "6 3/15",
                "6 4/15"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 14,
            "question": "Near the end of their journey, Timmy, Jenny, and Max found a hidden scroll. Which fraction on the scroll was an improper fraction?",
            "options": [
                "22/40",
                "457/612",
                "932/1009",
                "8/7"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 15,
            "question": "Max uncovered a hidden scroll with 4 1/10​. What is the improper fraction equivalent of this mixed fraction?",
            "options": [
                "42/10",
                "43/10",
                "41/10",
                "44/10"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 16,
            "question": "While traveling through Fraction Forest, the apprentices encountered 78/9. What is 78/9 in mixed fraction form?",
            "options": [
                "8 1/9",
                "8 3/9",
                "8 6/9",
                "8 7/9"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 17,
            "question": "Timmy the apprentice found a treasure chest containing a mixed fraction. The fraction was 7 6/9​. What is this mixed fraction as an improper fraction?",
            "options": [
                "65/9",
                "69/9​",
                "67/9",
                "71/9"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 18,
            "question": "While exploring deeper into the Fraction Forest, Timmy spotted 3 3/20​ carved on a stone. What does this mixed fraction simplify to as an improper fraction?",
            "options": [
                "63/20",
                "64/20",
                "65/20",
                "66/20"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 19,
            "question": "As they walked through the Fraction Forest, Timmy found a tree with a fraction carved into it. Which of the following fractions did Timmy find if it was an improper fraction?",
            "options": [
                "30/45",
                "25/31",
                "21/25",
                "70/10"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "questionNo": 20,
            "question": "Jenny found 61/7 ​ written on a magical tree in Fraction Forest. What is 61/7 as a mixed fraction?",
            "options": [
                "8 2/7",
                "8 6/7",
                "8 5/7",
                "8 3/7"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        }
    ]
    
    
    
    }
  ]
}
